...even if I didn't go to space, heh.
You know, l've got an lD card
and a NASA goIf shirt.
No, no. You gotta go.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)You can't turn down
an opportunity like this.
(Howard:)But what about the wedding...
(Howard:)...and all the money you put down
for the reception?
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)You let me worry about that.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)You go up to that space station
and you make me proud.
(Howard:)Um, okay.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)You got a problem with that?
(Howard:)All right, look,
I'm gonna level with you.
(Howard:)I'm terrified about going into space.
I mean, uh,
what if I don't make it back?
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)It's gonna be okay, son.
- You really think so?
- Of course.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)A pretty girl like Bernadette.
She'll find a new guy.